export const data = [
  {
    question: "Which bustling street in Singapore is famous for its vibrant mix of shops, street food stalls, and diverse cultural experiences?",
    option1: "Orchard Road",
    option2: "Little India",
    option3: "Haji Lane",
    option4: "Clarke Quay",
    ans: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "Which country governs Svalbard?",
    option1: "Norway",
    option2: "Russia",
    option3: "Sweden",
    option4: "Finland",
    ans: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "What is the nickname of Paris?",
    option1: "City of Love",
    option2: "City of Fashion",
    option3: "City of Music",
    option4: "City of Lights",
    ans: 4,
  },
  {
    question: "What is the indigenous name for New Zealand?",
    option1: "Kiwiland",
    option2: "Maoriland",
    option3: "Aotearoa",
    option4: "Zealandia",
    ans: 3,
  },
  {
    question: "Which is the lowest-lying country in the world?",
    option1: "Maldives",
    option2: "Netherlands",
    option3: "Bangladesh",
    option4: "Kiribati",
    ans: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Which animal is native to Madagascar?",
    option1: "Kangaroo",
    option2: "Penguin",
    option3: "Lemur",
    option4: "Tiger",
    ans: 3,
  },
  {
    question: "In which ocean are the Azores located?",
    option1: "Atlantic Ocean",
    option2: "Indian Ocean",
    option3: "Pacific Ocean",
    option4: "Arctic Ocean",
    ans: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "What is the famous architectural masterpiece in Barcelona designed by Antoni Gaud√≠?",
    option1: "Sagrada Familia",
    option2: "Louvre Museum",
    option3: "Colosseum",
    option4: "Acropolis",
    ans: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Which city is the capital of Denmark?",
    option1: "Oslo",
    option2: "Stockholm",
    option3: "Helsinki",
    option4: "Copenhagen",
    ans: 4,
  },
  {
    question: "What river runs through Dublin?",
    option1: "Seine",
    option2: "Thames",
    option3: "Liffey",
    option4: "Danube",
    ans: 3,
  },
];
